Guide to the Sheri Martinelli Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 1999 Acquisition, 1905-1993; 114.5; (127 boxes)+ 13 art, 1 broadside, 1 roll
  - Audiocassettes and Microcassettes, 1979-1993; Series VI; 78; (78 boxes)
    - Audiocassettes
      - "EP yg DP/olga 9/2/85", 1985 September 2; 1
      - "erase Jaz [illegible]", undated; 1
      - "gir delta copy o/p", undated; 1
      - "Itzhak Perlman", undated; 1
      - "O/M", undated; 1
      - "Ferry building bells break in", undated; 1
      - "Easter", undated; 1
      - "Easter 4/19/87 11 am Sunday", 1987 April 19; 2
      - "XX3", undated; 1
      - "Electra cont'd #2X", undated; 1
      - "Electra Soma Sheri Jan 26/87 Monday original", 1987 January 26; 1
      - "Electra from first long tape Readers Digest article", undated; 1
      - "Electra/Ariadne/Bu and Soma first take", undated; 1
      - "JAZ' xx1", undate; 1
      - "xx2", undated; 1
      - "Lawyer", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "Erase", undated; 1 (Box 88)
      - "Second tape with Dr of IZ", undated; 1
      - "Note re Shop 1 day go in and phone calls 6/20/79", 1979 June 20; 1
      - "T/teak wd art- delta G covers Dec 13, 1982", 1982 December 13; 1
      - "Stray thoughts scribble talk delta G/ di. P/ M./ etc.", undated; 1
      - "S's Thursday June 18. 1987", 1987 June 18; 1
      - "?", undated; 1
      - "EP/[illegible]/SM's Wed 10/20/93", 1993 October 20; 1
      - "to L is R", undated; 1
      - "Delta SM Lux Tate Ursula original", undated; 1
      - "Delta/TD", undated; 1
      - "Delta", undated; 1
      - "Delta gor O/P NYC", undated; 1
      - "November 9, 1982 T/ Z. T/SiBYL", 1982 November 9; 1
      - "November 9, 1982ECayo Ching", 1982 November 9; 1
      - "November 9, 1982 Kung/Pivot", 1982 November 9; 1
      - Kung, undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 4
      - "To GL'DYS 10/15/93 edit", 1993 October 15; 1 (Box 89)
      - "DDS 3 pm June 4, 1979 Monday glasses defend self - supermarket", 1979 June 4; 1
      - "DDS + [illegible] rap", undated; 1
      - "SM Reno male and Sue you male/what I must do", undated; 1
      - "SM Wednesday 8/14/85", 1985 August 14; 1
      - "SM talk delta TDH Sunday May 3, 1987", 1987 May 3; 1
      - "Round globe they travel in that", undated; 1
      - "T/earth romm experience", undated; 1
      - "T/travel [?]", undated; 1
      - "Delta gor SM/copy of O/P NYC", undated; 1
      - "Delta G T/wd covers 12/15/82 Wednesday", 1982 December 15; 1
      - "Motor", undated; 1
      - "Clear", undated; 1
      - "X", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 7
      - "Talk tape re: to both Mother and D last straw. Calif-men 3/4/83", 1983 May 4; 1 (Box 90)
      - "Noise after protest", undated; 1
      - "3/10/83 muffler trying to complain to T/landlord", 1983 March 10; 2
      - "Talk on T/name of EP greet", undated; 1
      - "Visitation original", undated; 1
      - "Morgan T. Sep.", undated; 1
      - "Sat [illegible] 3/12/83", 1983 March 12; 1
      - "A4", undated; 1
      - "A3", undated; 1
      - "A2", undated; 1
      - "A1", undated; 1
      - "Chatter with w/info Thursday 7/8/93 EVA", 1993 July 8; 1
      - "Boci bldg up to Boci letter Eve Thursday 7/8/93", 1993 July 8; 1
      - "Voice tape", undated; 1
      - "Aria Dimitre Lessons/Ana", undated; 1
      - "Dimitre-D/gods names", undated; 1
      - "Caruso Mario Lanza", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "Opera at of IZ Caruso", undated; 1 (Box 91)
      - "Was on machine day talk to Scott/ Canciones de mi Padre from T.V. L/R", undated; 1
      - "Original from SM T.V. to SM tape and from Lg L/R/Padre", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Sunday 10/24/93 Olga SM", 1993 October 24; 1
      - "Ice cream cones and Juke Box 8/27/93", 1993 August 27; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "P/T time/love SM May 7, 1987", 1987 May 7; 1
      - "14-Painter moving in /hurts knee at fence/bench SM Wednesday 8/26/92 on tape Eva/v. neg.", 1992 August 26; 1
      - "Erase", undated; 2
      - "Erase Thursday 1/11/84 Colorado, Kulch", 1984 January 11; 1
      - "Erase 1 poem only", undated; 1
      - "Jon E. Bronte", undated; 1
      - "Thaddeus Zielinski The SIBYL: 3 essays on ancient religion and Christianity", undated; 1
      - "Side 3 and 4", undated; 1
      - "5", undated; 1
      - "Zen notes to copy and idea tape", undated; 1
      - "Just talk rep. etc.", undated; 1
      - "Quit", undated; 1 (Box 92)
      - "P/agent", undated; 1
      - "Copy from other tapes ENG statement", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Copy from other tapes images", undated; 1
      - [Illegible], undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Delta gor Slime Mind", undated; 1
      - "Turq. grove Pow Wow music", 1978; 1
      - "Frank 7/9/86", 1986 July 9; 1
      - "Psychological problems of society and This is Frank & my A Sheri", undated; 1
      - "ENG 10/6/86 6:15 pm Monday "T/stars R bad etc. after Indian tape", 1986 October 6; 1
      - "Copy appeal Sheri August 29, 1986", 1986 August 29; 1
      - "Talk to oneself", undated; 2
      - "Zen/prophets/new", undated; 1
      - "SM talk and Zen outrage family, etc.", undated; 1
      - "Talk/P inspirational talk", undated; 2
      - "Inspirational talk/P S/C", undated; 1
      - "At night when M was here. The one night when made a tape", undated; 1 (Box 93)
      - "SAT 7/13/85 EP knows + / cantos JAZ", 1985 July 13; 1
      - "Thursday May 3, 1979 2 pm, Friday May 4, 1979 AM", 1979 May 3; 1
      - "Sunday May 6, 1979 May 7, 1979 Monday", 1
      - "Sunday May 6, 1979 at high noon before it", 1979 May; 1
      - "Thursday May 3, 1979 AM first one", 1979 May 3; 1
      - "Thursday May 3, 1979 AM", 1979 May 3; 1
      - "Monday night May Day 10:30 Monday and Tuesday at creek at night", undated; 1
      - "Wednesday May 2, 1979 First", 1979 May 2; 1
      - "Pre-appointment talk--food poisoning illness phone call G. opposing 6/30/79 Saturday", 1979 June 30; 1
      - "Go my Lellee tape first/ Sunday April 29, 1979 Joe/p-[illegible]-be a scene", 1979 April 29; 1
      - "Sunday April 29, 1979 erase a word think was last tape", 1979 April 29; 1
      - "Planes/gas/etc. Sunday 5/13/79", 1979 MAy 13; 1
      - "Of out #2 tape voice", undated; 1
      - "Family 2", undated; 1
      - "On at beginning. Logic/g. caps at end laugh at B/work", undated; 1
      - "Wednesday early 2/79 did not get used got skipped over", 1979 February; 1
      - "Wednesday center second May 2/79", 1979 February; 1
      - [Illegible] "P.M. / Wednesday May 2, 1979", 1979 May 2; 1
      - "September 26, 1986 c/93 and air letter copy SM", undated; 1
      - "Friday September 26/1986 c/93 #2", 1
      - "P and E (NG.) canto talk Friday September 26, 1986 c/93 Lox etc.", 1986 September 26; 1
      - "For end", undated; 1 (Box 94)
      - "September 26/1986 Fri c/93 & air letter #2", 1986 September 26; 1
      - "Copy from tape #3, Salty abt relatives", undated; 1
      - "Talk 8/8/85", 1985; 1
      - "Abt T/cantos/not [illegible], undated; 1
      - "Delta gallery", undated; 1
      - "Started Monday September 29, 1986", 1986 September 29; 1
      - "Copy red tapes and erase October 1, 1986", 1986 October 1; 1
      - "OK side, no record", undated; 1
      - "S+M", undated; 1
      - "Female stuff September 16, 1986", 1986 September 16; 1
      - "Wail", undated; 1
      - "July 16, 1985 Delta G", 1985 July 16; 1
      - "July 13, 1985 SAT Delta G'p", 1985 July 13; 1
      - "Talk /JAZ Yin coffee/tap and SMK talk September 13, 1985. Morning sun in heart of hearts in the heartland continued", 1985 September 13; 1
      - "September 22, 1985 a note on Delta G bows", 1985 September 22; 1
      - "Talk papers "B'day" Friday 9/6/85 and night up and talk", 1985 September 6; 1
      - "Continued Sunday September 15, 1985 starts need coffee", 1985 September 15; 1
      - "September 15, 1985 continued Sunday", 1985 September; 1
      - "Personal life things get off mind", undated; 1
      - "October 22, 1986 DP/Monday SciFic", 1986 October 22; 1 (Box 95)
      - "That's my girls EP listen", undated; 1
      - "Delta", undated; 1
      - "Saturday evening September 14, 1985 A/Plum", 1985 September 14; 1
      - "Saturday evening September 14, 1985 B/Y Plum", 1985 September 14; 1
      - "Quote places in Cantos 85 and to end of Cantos August 2, 1895", 1985 August 2; 1
      - "From letters notes Delta G", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "September 26, 1986", 1986 September 26; 1
      - "LMM", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "September 15, 1986 DP'm May Sinclair idea copy", 1986 September 15; 1
      - September 15, 1986 P/B and E/ENG art etc. copy, 1986 September 15; 1
      - "September 15, 1986 S+M art etc. copy", 1986 September 15; 1
      - "September 15, 1986 infamy day need copy", 1986 September 15; 1
      - "I ching 1", undated; 1
      - "1/2", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Apollonious/Tyana 11/12/85", 1985 November 12; 1
      - "T/Buke of Sheri 1/no at end 2/wavers", undated; 1
      - "SM Buke, changeable and slow", undated; 1 (Box 96)
      - "1 HD", undated; 1
      - "2 HD Vg + Ug visit HD cont to 1-HD", undated; 1
      - "copy appeal to Sheri August 29, 1986 listen to END this side", 1986 August 29; 2
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "September 1, 1986 file copy DP'm", 1986 September; 1
      - "c/93", undated; 1
      - "September 1, 1986 6 AM DP'M", 1986 September; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Science Fiction", undated; 1
      - "End of DP'm HW. Delta G more c/93 c/93 end of comment", undated; 1
      - "August 15, 1986 Delta G, HW and DP'm my Cantos endish, D old Joe Gould c/93", 1986 August 15; 1
      - "August 1 & 2, 1986 original NOT sent sent part in copy S and M/SM Eddie Shu EP etc interrupts", 1986 August; 1
      - "Copy C Flora Canto, Delta G tape J. Gould c/93-93 For SM file terr hours D'Pman and HW side 1 of Delta tape", undated; 1
      - "erase my side of it take 2 not good", undated; 1
      - "erase my side of it not good", undated; 1
      - "M+TC of ENG out/street", undated; 1
      - "TS Keetoowah erase/listen", undated; 1
      - "TS poem Keetoowah", undated; 1 (Box 97)
      - "2/on before Tom Keetoowah", undated; 1
      - "Indian talk", undated; 1
      - "Copy on SM tape copy", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Goes with Cantos tape material SM etc. Zen #c", undated; 1
      - "Re/art and A Tao wat of my story Zen", undated; 1
      - "Zen August 1986 ENG", 1986 August; 1
      - "Zen #2 Zen a", undated; 1
      - "Zen B #3", undated; 1
      - "as if to EP in making for all Zen bits in here", undated; 1
      - "Zen bits", undated; 1
      - "Sheri tape must listen Zen ideas practical", undated; 1
      - "File copy travel appeal in that Sheri August 29, 1986", 1986 August 29; 1
      - "RedGone potlatch/file copy/end appeal and talk tape P", undated; 1
      - "1 E yale s/quiet week August 13/17 side 2/5/13-17 79/E", undated; 1
      - "ug/at BBQ S+Co. Art scene last Wednesday August 22", undated; 1
      - "1/DDS scene in retrospect", undated; 1
      - "First Delta He not but they are", undated; 1
      - "Delta", undated; 1
      - "New/Delta", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1 (Box 98)
      - "Friday end at America", undated; 1
      - "Friday May 4/79", 1979 May 4; 1
      - "Wednesday May 9, 1979-sign painter-PM", 1979 May 9; 1
      - "Wednesday 9-1979/Friday May 11/79 2/AM"", 1
      - "1/2", uncated; 1
      - "Tom Sharp 958 Addison Palo Alto, CA 94301 351-5132 Questions about Ezra Pound and Louis Zukofsky", undated; 1
      - "May 7 Monday 79 Tuesday May 8 P.M. scrolls letter still", 1979 May 7; 1
      - "Tuesday May 8 79 AM scrolls Tuesday May 8 Wednesday May 9 AM and AM", 1979; 1
      - "Wednesday May 9, 1979 AM Balleys out slow", 1
      - "The letters answer Monday May 7, 1979 D letter", 1979 May 7; 1
      - "Copy from 8/18/86 ENG Monday tape", 1986 August 18; 1
      - "Monday August 18, 1986 ENG part a NSR letter", 1986 August 18; 1
      - "Copy Monday", undated; 1
      - "All kinds of things ENG answer/ letter August 23, 1986 Saturday #2", 1986 August 23; 1
      - "All kinds of things ENG answer/ letter August 23, 1986 Saturday #1", 1986 August; 1
      - "Tuesday 26 August 1986 ENG liniv Cantos", 1986 August; 1
      - "ENG Sibyla Bubbles Wednesday 16 July 1986 Silly Talk to AGS 1986 more Silly Talk", 1986 July; 1
      - "Case August 13, 1986 Wednesday #1", 1986 August 13; 1
      - "Case #2", undated; 1
      - "Case noise-box 3", undated; 1
      - "ND August 14, 1986 Faint beg ENG #1", 1986 August 14; 1 (Box 99)
      - "ND ENG #2", undated; 1
      - "6/26/86 ENG one second at a time that each second is different/some C/PU ideogram/B video", 1986 June 26; 1
      - "July 1, 1986", 1986 July 1; 1
      - "ENG mid rule talk somber tune tone", undated; 1
      - "ENG Tuesday 7/22/86", 1986 July 22; 1
      - "6/4/86 Wednesday tape fades", 1986 June 4; 1
      - "August 12, 1986 ENG memories California", 1986 August 12; 1
      - "Sunday morning perceptions", undated; 1
      - "Saturday August 9, 1986 ENG NZ", 1986 August 9; 1
      - "Friday August 8, 1986 Mayan for DR", 1986 August 8; 1
      - "Some music and entertainment", undated; 1
      - "Ind.\T.V. and other fragments", undated; 1
      - "a prayer? SM's Thursday March 7, 1991 7 AM "Divine Breach", 1991 March 7; 1
      - 1 & 2 Corinthians, 1980; 1
      - Acts 1-17:15 read by Efrom Zimbalist, Jr., 1980; 1
      - Romans, 1980; 1
      - Galatians and Ephesians, 1980; 1
      - Acts 17:16-28, 1980; 1
      - Philippians through Philemon, 1980; 1
      - Revelation, 1980; 1
      - Hebrews, 1980; 1 (Box 100)
      - James through Jude, 1980; 1
      - John 1-10, 1980; 1
      - Matthew 1-18, 1980; 1
      - Matthew 19-28, 1980; 1
      - Luke 14-24, 1980; 1
      - Mark 1-16, 1980; 1
      - John 11-21, 1980; 1
      - Luke 1-13, 1980; 1
      - DG, undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "4/8/83 Friday G and fighting", 1983 April 8; 1
      - "4/8/83 Friday", 1983 April 8; 1
      - "Started 19 March 1983 G/Chris + Marshmallows G", 1
      - "copy", undated; 1
      - "copy SM EP cantos delta G", undated; 1
      - "Original", undated; 1
      - "On tape G rest", undated; 1
      - "5/5/83 Thursday G/Terrorization Real El Camino\This Side check AA B2", 1983 May 5; 1
      - "5/5/83 Thursday G at end 3 hrs terrorization check this side AA side B1", 1983 May 5; 1
      - "Anyone [illegible] their German these EP etc./ tape funks out on SM tape", undated; 1
      - "Strange voice on tape/Orono #1", undated; 1 (Box 101)
      - "Orono #2", undated; 1
      - "Orono #3", undated; 1
      - "From SM tape Friday September 4/beg. noise/spider legs FOTO September 26 art to P copy on Pete police +1x FOTO", undated; 1
      - "2x", undated; 1
      - "To S+M re:T/Terrell + Lux + Ursula Sheri 6/24/85", 1985 June 24; 1
      - "Around 6/24/85 talking to Stephan", 1985 June 24; 1
      - "Jot from T.V.", undated; 1
      - "P/talk 1-88", undated; 1
      - "Jos C/Myths/Time 12-27-91 T/court of love Tristan and Isolt", 1991 December 27; 1
      - "Jos Campbell Myths through time Friday 12-7-91/ch 26", undated; 1
      - "1 tape of Cayce Bk Greece ruled by which", undated; 1
      - "Sudden art tape 1/11/87", 1987 January 11; 1
      - "HW Meyer talk Delta RW end hey 12/86 1-87", 1986-1987; 1
      - "From SM tapes/talk art S.Pt/NJ", undated; 1
      - "HW 1/17/87", 1987 January 17; 1
      - "For T/video saddest letter EP+T/at stables Monticello", undated; 1
      - "EP DAWOO and Chas/Shutz", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "SM talk", undated; 2
      - "For T/video talk on nothing but The News c/93", 1993; 1 (Box 102)
      - "Hem", undated; 1
      - "Notes for prelude to last Canto", undated; 1
      - "U of T at A re/papers", undated; 1
      - "Notes re T/papers", undated; 2
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "India/Iraq Sunday February 2, 1992", 1992 February 2; 2
      - "China #1 Egypt #1", undated; 1
      - "China #2 Egypt #2", undated; 1
      - "Elusis/Athens #1 Monday February 3, 1992", 1992 February 3; 1
      - "Last 2 HRS of P(L)ogram", undated; 1
      - "Start 4/5/78 EP/HD 4 Dav gor", 1978; 1
      - "Dav gor Art", undated; 1
      - "Art is - Cadmus line + half pie moon tape one A half pie moon ends suddenly tape 1-A", undated; 1
      - "A Tag end of "Art", undated; 1
      - "Note for lawyer", undated; 1
      - "Notes re: T/cow visit t/Bore CowBore Tuesday 2/4/92", 1992 February; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "8/30/87 for Authority on here HJ2", 1987 August 30; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "G + fallback to Gin (after Kuliafi day scene) 1/23/92 Thursday", 1992 January; 1 (Box 103)
      - "EP's SM Thursday 3-19/92", 1992 March; 1
      - "Poet/read/old awful mush awful reading!", undated; 1
      - "To + for S+M/T?old poems from early mind states when v. young she", undated; 1
      - "Copy awful noise S+M poems sorry", undated; 1
      - "Note of saying all odd experiences to DG", undated; 1
      - "Continued from odd exp to DG odd exp. and to this pt.", undated; 1
      - "SM talk Rough talk at beginning", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "SM to Marcia 1/26/87", 1987; 1
      - "Ariadne Milkweed talk re Cantos", undated; 1
      - "Davgor general policy DG", undated; 1
      - "T/strange voice + only copy some of T/ copied from +AA Sunday June 92 8:30 AM-10 AM get up at 5:30 or 5:45 AM!", 1992 June; 1
      - "Talk god etc./Zen orono sm tapes/GD fruits Yasdrasail tree life", undated; 1
      - "Mind states alive Zen", undated; 1
      - "Cayce 2 monk+purple+white", undated; 1
      - "A talk re: abortion Sheri Martinelli 'Last Protege of Ezra Pound,' Tuesday July 7, 1992", 1992 July 7; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Abortion SM", undated; 1
      - "EP's usury Canto "Addendum for C" by Sheri Martinelli", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Original Ellens", undated; 1 (Box 104)
      - "Ellens", undated; 1
      - "T.V. T/spirit oonabega", undated; 1
      - "G.A.M. Thursday 9/10/92", 1992 September 10; 1
      - "T/usura cantos SM Wednesday 7/8/92 #1", 1992 July 8; 1
      - "Usura Cantos EP SM original/edit #2", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Saturday 9/19/92 T/DRM/Father/Sister/ Chiefs Circle 11 AM", 1992 September 19; 1
      - "1/5/92 SM=a serious character S-C #1", 1992 January 5; 1
      - "Serious character SM S.C. #2", undated; 1
      - "Olga ends at v. beg?", undated; 1
      - "Delta gor #1", undated; 1
      - "Delta gor #2", undated; 1
      - "Fone tape 1/21/92/Maria +SM #1 Merrell Lynch tire glass Thursday 2/13/92 phone #1", 1992; 1
      - "Phone #2 Kitty 11-10/Sherry some sun gemo award center/Sunday 10/6/91 12 noon G and M call G calls/San Diego Saturday 6/29/91 LA/quake +T/TX female Maria EP letters ANSR my T/Sun 10/6/91 GDM Cal 12 noon/G calls", 1991; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Fone lawyers Tuesday and 2/25/92/SM 2 talk/last one erase/T/phone Beep is Noise use", 1992; 1
      - "P/SM vision Friday 6/19/87", 1987 June 19; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "T", undated; 1 (Box 105)
      - "B lib", undated; 1
      - "#1", undated; 1
      - Frederic Chopin-Piano Concerto No. 2 in F minor, Andante spianato and Grande Polonaise, Op. 22 Nocturne in C sharp minor, Op. posth Tamas Vasry, piano, Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra, Conductor: Janos Kulka. Polydor International, 1964, 1977; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "There is no etc. to all St. Ment.", undated; 1
      - "Copy/P", undated; 1
      - "P", undated; 2
      - "P/1/17/87", 1987 January 17; 1
      - "P/B/E(ng) RA set 9:30 AM 11/20/86", 1986 November 20; 1
      - "To Pete Soapbox re: "war" verse Ra set- information copy P 11/20/86 EP Boris letters", 1986 November 20; 1
      - "P lots", undated; 1
      - "Copy", undated; 1
      - "P/11/23/86", 1986 November 23; 1
      - "P from SM (night talk) tape/end Jaz tape TSE meals galleries etc. from tape Q", undated; 1
      - "#2 Sanyo copy", undated; 1
      - "L mach", undated; 1
      - #1B Sanyo mach., undated; 1
      - "#2/B Large tape copy", undated; 1
      - "P 5AM talk at idea woman", undated; 1
      - "Battery ran out/listen and note of T/ Delta G call", undated; 1 (Box 106)
      - "Thursday 1/26/82 #1", 1982 January 26; 1
      - "Thursday 1/26/82 #2", 1982 January 26; 1
      - "Mder and Bder and company Plain talk #2", undated; 1
      - "12/3/81 M/B/der #3", 1981 December 3; 1
      - "#4--#6", undated; 3
      - "Mder and Bder and company Plain Talk AM 12/3/81 tape 1", 1981 December 3; 1
      - "Mder #1/60", undated; 1
      - "Mush Pai! Mary", undated; 1
      - "?", undated; 1
      - "1 Delta G T/second tape", undated; 1
      - "1/Delta G gold cloth real first tape letter/Dioce 6/24/81", 1981 June 24; 1
      - "Gr Delta 7/9/81", 1981 July 9; 1
      - "On S/1 but?", undated; 1
      - "D", undated; 1
      - "A Christmas letter", undated; 1
      - "Half used some rec tape bad stuck", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "J1 #1", undated; 1
      - "J1 #1-2", undated; 1 (Box 107)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 6
      - "Monday October 1/85 October 6/85", 1985 October; 1
      - "Fone 6/10/92 Wednesday G/M House", 1992 June 10; 1
      - "Copied phone messages 6/12/93 to 11 AM-ish (nursing home Fa Ch girl) Sleepy Hollow/G talk/A-A-1/Se Hal Home girl and then T/strange voice? Robo T/ first G+SM talk after hear tape girl in home then robot and voice?", 1993 June; 1
      - "Copied from tape phone 6/12/92 2 pm phone 6/13/92 6-11/114 Thursday/M phone mate mystery/Paul Answer/Maria and B. Neelson/Bg 5 Mystery microtape G on M's phone mate and comments", 1992 June; 1
      - "Fone 6/5/92 Friday Morry and Gil talk about House etc. 6/6/92 Sheri calls Edna 6//6/92", 1992 June; 1
      - "re: Nursing Home girl and G talk N and SM Sleepy Hollow phone and talk 6-12 or 13-92 AA2", 1992 June; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "Talk", undated; 1
      - "Moon, woman, Saturn", undated; 1
      - The Four Seasons Op. 8, No. 1-4 by Antonio Vivaldi. Hamburg Chamber Orchestra, Wilfred Bottcher, Conductor, Pina Carmiretti, Solo Violin, undated; 1
      - "#1-2", undated; 2
      - "#2", undated; 1 (Box 108)
      - "Ind. music", undated; 1
      - "Ind. music taken off of large machine", undated; 1
      - "Home after 2:30 pm E.S.T. 5/31/78 Wednesday phone call here was 11:30 AM copied Turq. and Y's-growls 2 Ind for George. Original used for solstice tape copied for home", 1978; 1
      - "Incantation solstice 6/78", 1978 June; 1
      - "Lib (3) T original/EP and Lg bks/ casual", undated; 1
      - "Art folio copy", undated; 1
      - "Stop here to P re letter", undated; 1
      - "Eva ends half way 1 over Bk very wordy poem", undated; 1
      - "#2 Eva ends EP on top #2", undated; 1
      - "Extra notes copy fr erase JE to copy", undated; 1
      - "1 erase testing Greek", undated; 1
      - "Yale again tape #2", undated; 1
      - "TSE", undated; 1
      - "EP TV", undated; 1
      - "P C/R new", undated; 1
      - "P/C/R new talk family sister etc.", undated; 1
      - "BR wds tape all side beginning sneeze talk/backwards tape", undated; 1
      - "EP poem Anima Sola for J fleet", undated; 1
      - "Backwards tape to halfway", undated; 1
      - "Copy 1 for Eva B/art lesson 1/+ Rev t/goat screaming lesson 2/+wolves being hunted by helicopter lesson 3/add trailer of "art by SM etc", undated; 1
      - "Start Eva ice skates Thursday April 27", undated; 1
      - "Thursday 4/20/78 Eva photos cull/ 2 plays backwards", 1978 April 20; 1 (Box 109)
      - "To E.M. J+J+JJ Monday April 24\wolf tape", undated; 1